[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This medical term refers to a disease-causing protein agent that contains no genetic material.", "correct_answer": "Prion", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemma", "Papule", "Alper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a normal fasting blood sugar?", "correct_answer": "Less than 100 mg/dl (5.6 mmol/L)", "incorrect_answers": ["Less than 160 mg/dl (8.9 mmol/L)", "Less than 140 mg/dl (7.8 mmol/L)", "Less than 125 mg/dl (6.9 mmol/L)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the address of the Goonies House?", "correct_answer": "368 -38th Street", "incorrect_answers": ["361 -38th Street", "366 -38th Street", "363 -38th Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of the strict water preserving mechanisms, the cactus dies within hours after a part of it is broken or damaged.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nominees won the 1980 Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor?", "correct_answer": "Neil Diamond for The Jazz Singer", "incorrect_answers": ["Kirk Douglas for Saturn 3", "Richard Dreyfuss for The Competition", "Anthony Hopkins for A Change of Seasons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to propose the idea of a metric system?", "correct_answer": "Simon Stevin", "incorrect_answers": ["Gabriel Mouton", "Napoleon", "King Louis XIV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1954 a British group released a full length animated version of this George Orwell novel.", "correct_answer": "Animal Farm", "incorrect_answers": ["In the Trenches", "Down and Out in London and Paris", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hyenas were domesticated and eaten in ancient Egypt.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Forrest Gump was based on a novel published several years before the movie was released.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following four disorders are actually different names for the same disease. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Maniac", "incorrect_answers": ["Antisocial Personality", "Psychopath", "Sociopath"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Demographically, the Netherlands matches which of this characteristics?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Its population is first in average height in the world.", "It is one of most densely populated countries in the world.", "It is one of the most densely cabled countries in the world."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most medical authorities believe that coffee consumption is harmful to the health.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]